Severin Yehor

UI/UX designer



About

I am UI/UX designer with 1.7 years practicing in creating mobile and web interfaces. For me wide UX research plays a crucial role in quality design, problem-solving and decision-making process. Comfort and simplicity of design are also important to me, which includes not only creativity, but also calculating pixels and following development rules.

Portfolio

Behance

Behance(NovlaSoft)

Dribbble

Contacts

Email: yehorseverin@gmail.com/jagaur@ukr.net

Telegram (+380 98 578 31 79)

LinkedIn

Experience

NovlaSoft UI/UX Designer

12.2022 - NOW

The company specializes in creating mobile applications for IOS

Responsibilities:

- Market/competitor analysis
- CJM, user persona, information architecture, user flow
- Wireframing and prototyping
- Creation of logo
- UI design and creation of design system
- UI design of App Store screens

Upwork Freelance UI/UX designer 09.2021 - 12.2022

Responsibilities:

- Creation of icons and banners
- Creation of logos
- CJM, information architecture, user flow
- Wireframing and prototyping
- Ui design and UI kit
- Moodboards
- Prototyping

Education & Certifications

Google

<u>Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design</u> 24.01.2022

Creative Practice

<u>UX/UI. Projecting and design of interfaces</u> 16.04.2022

ProjectorMobile Apps Design

04.2023 - Now

Skills

Hard:

- UI/Ux
- Figma
- Photoshop(beginner)
- Miro
- Trello
- Adobe XD
- Readymag
- User persona, Interviews, LO-Fi & HI-FI wireframing
- Animation in Figma
- Material Design/HID
- UI kit
- Html/Css

Soft:

- Adaptation
- Empathy

- Open-Mindedness
- Active Listening
- English B1 / Ukrainian native